Cheng-Han Yang Site: https://leonfantc.herokuapp.com/ Phone: (614) 360-3248 Email: yang.3028@osu.edu

Address: 1150 Kinnear Rd, Apt. 1225C, Columbus, OH 43212

PERSONAL SUMMARY

Excels in organizational planning and developing. Experienced working collaboratively with people in diverse backgrounds to accomplish common goals. Enhances quality and determination of a team by developing project outline and making critical decision. Provides fast, reliable and requirement-oriented software projects.

OBJECTIVE

Seeking an internship opportunity. Available starting May 2017; open to relocation.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Cloud Engineering Internship, YPCloud, Taipei, Taiwan, June/2016 – August/2016

- Planned and presented an exhibition for 100 invertors, future investors and engineers regarding cloud service
- Cooperated with senior software engineers to build a cloud computing application (Cloud video convertor)
- Led a team of 7 individuals to elaborate a script of IOT service and achieved goals within two months
- Responsible for demonstrating methods used in cloud service to future investors

Instructional Assistant, The Ohio State University, OH – Aug/2016 – Present

- Assist over 80 students to succeed in system and networking courses
- Prepare projects and lead students to right paths with proper inputs; work 13 − 17 hours per week

INDIVIDUAL PROJECTS

Computer Networking Projects, The Ohio State University, Columbus, OH, Jan/2016 – Present

- Implemented a messenger application using Java and TCP/IP protocol
- Constructed TCP based on UDP, such as checksum algorithm, delta-timer and circular buffer implementations
- Socket programming to build a system-like IOT to provide passages for communication of various objects

Shopping Website Development, May/2014 - Aug/2014

- Created an online shopping mall that manages CRM using Java
- Designed a website using JS, html and backend information management using MySQL

OSU Garage Website Development, Aug /2016 – Dec/2016

- Built a website that keeps track of available parking space on OSU campus
- Constructed back-end management with Ruby on Rails including database, page routing and testing

Android App Development, Oct/2015 – Jan/2016

- Develop educational products and function-oriented tools such as Riemann sum calculator
- Responsible for light CPU load programming and user friendly UI design

LEADERSHIP

Big Data Case Competitions, The Ohio State University, Columbus, OH, Nov/2015 – Present

- Lead a team of four individuals working for local companies to mine data and find potential trend
- Provide ideas to other members on project development and future measures
- Deliver presentations regarding findings to companies that points out pros and cons

EDUCATION

The Ohio State University, OH – Dec/2017 GPA: 3.1 Last Semester GPA: 3.5

B.S. Computer Science Engineering

CORE QUALIFICATIONS

- Fine skills in backend web development using Java, Python, SQL, Ruby on Rails and frontend using html and JS
- Experience in socket programming and cloud computing development with TCP/IP protocol
- Comfortable developing with C, C++ and Android SDK

ACTIVITIES

Guitarist, Band Member, Feb/2015 – Present

Perform rock and roll songs for non-profit organizations at no charge